{
    "id": "262c5a9cae4a4a92bdaeb1754bd2c21d",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He made a handsome donation ............................. the flood relief fund.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He quarreled with me .................................... a trivial issue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not satisfied ................................... your explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "with",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must not be envious ................................... your neighborâ€™s success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We can only rely ............................... our own efforts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must be prompt ................................. carrying out orders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Recently there has been a sharp rise .................................... the price of gold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was born ....................................... poor parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His views do not accord .................................. mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Temperance and employment are conducive ........................................ health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}